Register of the Vitaliano Bernardino Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1951-1977. (Box 5-9)
  - Southeast Asian Ministers of Education Organization. Arranged chronologically.
    - A Report on the External Evaluation of SEAMEO Units, Bangkok, August, 1976., Bound mimeographed copy.
    - Report of the SEAMES Director's 1976 Fund-Raising Mission, Bangkok, December 1976., Mimeographed copy.
    - SEAMES Director's Annual Report, Bangkok, 1976., Bound mimeographed copy.
    - Development Plan of SEAMEO Project in Archelogoy and Fine Arts, Bangkok, 1977., Bound mimeographed copy.
    - Twelfth Conference of the SEAMEO: Final Report, Djakarta, March 3 - 7, 1977., Bound mimeographed copy.
    - Revised Proposed Development Plan for SEAMEO Programme in Non-Formal Education (SNEP), September 1977., Mimeographed copy.
  - Teacher Trainigs
    - Asian Institute for Teacher Educators (UNESCO), Regional Symposium on the In-Service Training of Primary School Teachers in Asia: Final Report, University of the Philippines, Quezon City, July 5 - 19, 1967., Bound mimeographed copy.
    - Pines, E.A., Basic Principles of Rural Teacher Training, n.d., Mimeographed copy.
  - Vietnam
    - Republic of Vietnam, Ministry of Education, Projects for Reconstruction Rehabilitation and Development in Education, Saigon, 1973.
      - Copy I.
      - Copy II.
- INCREMENT, 1949-1953
  - Philippine Islands, Bureau of Public Schools, Bulletin (Box 9)
    - Community Improvement through the Public Schools, August 3, 1949., Photocopy.
    - Leadership Training for Life-Centered Education in Gagayan, May 29, 1950., Photocopy.
    - The Organization and Operation of the Community-Centered School, September 19, 1950., Photocopy.
    - Establishing Community Reading Centers, October 17, 1950., Photocopy.
    - Enriching and Vitalizing the Curriculum for the Improvement of Community Living, May 3, 1951., Photocopy.
    - Report on Adult Education in Action, Theme of the 42nd Annual Convention of Division of Superintendents, September 28, 1951., Photocopy.
    - Fundamental Education through Community-Centered Schools in the Philippines, October 11, 1951., Photocopy.
    - Professional Literature for Teachers, Principals, and Supervisors on the Community-Centered Schools and Related Topics, September 11, 1952., Photocopy.
    - Adult Education - Its Community School Development Program, September 13, 1952., Photocopy.
    - Achievements of the Community School for the School Year 1951-1952, December 16, 1952., Photocopy.
    - What the Community School Might Well Emphasize during the School Year 1953-1954, October 30, 1953., Photocopy.
- AUDIO-VISUAL, 1954.
  - 1 print of Philippine community school. (Box 10 A-V)